Gen!
Yeah?
Will you take these vegetables to Old Lü?
Sure.
I'm Xiaobai, your teacher.
I'm the interpretator.
On today's lesson,
we'll learn what not to eat.
What are those supposed to be?
Peace and Quiet
Grandpa, don't disturb my lesson!
I'll see myself out.
I've brought some things for demonstration.
Which you're eating...
Please! You must listen to me!
You can't eat that.
Why?
Because if you don't listen, you can't stay.
Don't feel bad!
If you get hungry,
I'll give you lots of wood to eat.
So be a good boy!
I will! I will!
Looks like he's food motivated...
Don't translate this.
This is convenient!
It's a shame it caused so much damage.
A shark?!
It's no shark.
It's quite big...
A water spirit?
Was it drawn here by the flood?
Or driven out from the village by it...
I hope it can understand me...
Stay away!
Shoot...
Now I've gone and done it.
Ancestral Shrine of
The Wei Family
Get out of there!
Can I eat this?
Of course, you can eat this.
Xiaohei, you're back!
Have you healed enough for today?
Yeah.
You can eat it.
Wow.
How about that? I'm a good teacher.
Sure.
Thanks to Heixiu!
Can I eat this?
Yeah...
Is he going to keep asking?
I feel we'll have a problem...
Can I eat this?
Go ahead, but...
You don't need to ask every time.
Bidiu!
Did you know?
If you eat too much, you'll get stuck in one place.
What?!
I didn't know that...
You actually believed that?
It's gone.
Seems he's on his way.
What?!
Was that your ability now?
Like this.
Wow...
Awesome!
You can get food without getting out of bed!
Bidiu's scared stiff...
I found him.
Where is he?
100 miles southwest.
Are you sure it's him?
He fits your description.
Ice type by appearance.
We'll look into it first.
Why look for him?
Laojun announced that the Sky Pearl
was taken the day after we went there.
So what?
If Diting and Xuanli were there,
who could have taken the Pearl from them?
Laojun could.
Fine. Who else could?
Diting is Laojun's guard dog.
Xuanli isn't.
So you think Xuanli took the Pearl?
I'm 60 percent sure.
So we must look into it.
But if it's really Xuanli,
we can't stand up against him.
Head-on attacks are not my style.
'Cause you're weak at close combat?
Silence.
The flood has finally gone!
Let's go!
We'll need to tear down the whole roof...
Power Struggle
It's gonna be big work...
Are you sure I can't ask Laojun for compensation?
Don't worry.
It's not that big a deal.
I can fix it easily.
My saved money...
The house gets much more light now.
So should I build an open-air kitchen?
No.
I'd die of heat when the air con doesn't run.
Air
con
It seems it will be very hot today.
Xiaobai!
I'll do the sweeping.
You bring two watermelons from Big Ji's.
Okay.
All set.
Let's go!
Hello, Auntie Cow!
Good morning, meow!
Good afternoon, meow!
Good evening, meow, meow, meow!
Enemy detected.
We're almost there.
Found you!
So, Gen finally wants to challenge me?
I'm here for watermelons.
Welcome.
This way, please.
New guys arrived.
At last, someone to bully.
I'll sweep later...
Xiaohei, keep an eye on Bidiu!
I will.
They're here.
Get them!
Are these two fine?
What you choose is perfect.
Only you guys are home?
Dad and Mom are out at the watermelon fields.
What's with these guys?
Why didn't you tell me he's that strong?
Would you have believed me?
I still can't believe it!
Exactly!
It found us!
This one's not so bad!
What do we do?
Run!
We're already running!
A gathering?
What the heck is this?
There you go.
Thanks, Big Ji!
Let's go!
Heixiu, where's everyone else?
Well, well. A cat beat you?
You're useless.
Told you not to mess with us, cats!
He's stronger than you!
You talk like a loser!
Then fight him!
You don't scare me!
And who gave you that scar on your face?
What about yours?
I got it when I tripped!
We tripped up together!
Is that him?
He looks weak.
You'll regret that.
Listen, newcomer. I am...
You're so insolent!
Brother Gray was careless.
But I will...
Boss!!
They're home.
So Xiaohei found Bidiu?
Let's hurry back!
What happened here?
The flood has damaged the ancestral shrine?
Yes.
The mayor's asking for donations.
Okay.
I'll be there shortly.
The ancestral shrine?
Yes.
Everyone's home is in a mess now.
I'm afraid no one can donate.
I almost forgot about it...
What are you doing up there?
Looking if we have some money left.
It's all right.
I'll take care of it.
You?
You just tell the mayor about it.
I'll renovate the shrine.
How do you get money?
As far as I know, we've got a check.
So we can claim it?
Sure.
This would be a great help for the village.
It's nothing...
We're leaving now!
You're going too...?
There's a bus to town anyway.
And I can visit Shan Xin.
Isn't it dangerous?
Don't worry.
It's weird you have clothes on.
You say it like I usually had none on.
City Park
Is this really the place?
It should be, according to the address...
Children!
Who are you looking for?
Good morning! We'd like to meet the manager.
Do you have an appointment?
No.
Access card?
We've got it!
Is this it?
It's from Laojun.
Where are your parents?
No good?
Children.
A paper with a scribble on is not an access card.
Is this supposed to be a joke?
It's not completely impossible...
So what do we do now?
Just go home?
We'll have to sneak in.
Just get further from the gate.
Bidiu!
We can get in from here.
But this wall's quite tall...
How do we get in?
Xiaohei can help.
Come here!
He's inside!
He's looking for a landing place.
I'll go in first.
Wait, and don't move.
We're inside!
Xiaohei, you're awesome!
It's like the forest all over again.
Yeah.
We'd be here if we entered at the gate.
Now we should be around here.
Our destination is here.
We don't know the scale of the map.
But we'll need to pass a hill.
Looks pretty far away...
Wait a minute! Xiaohei could teleport us there!
My limit is 5 yards at the moment...
I see...
This is strange...
The trees here are bigger than the ones in the mountain.
They're at least several hundred years old.
They must be well taken care of, right?
No, they're unnaturally big.
Xiaobai, look at this!
Coming!
We're that high already?
Maybe I can see our house.
That's the visitor's office, according to the map.
Those buildings in the distance must be our destination.
There should be spirits there.
Let's head over.
Someone should find us once we're closer.
What should we do then?
That's why we came, to find someone.
Oh, right.
We've found someone.
Are you first-time visitors?
Yes.
Who introduced you to us?
Laojun.
Do you know him?
Naturally.
That means you are Lord Xuanli.
Please, call me Gen.
Excuse us for breaking in.
Don't worry about it.
Everyone enters like that.
I am Tu Bei, the secretary.
Our hall manager has been waiting for you.
Please follow me.
Hall manager?
This reminds me of Laojun's place.
What did you mean by this, sir?
A tiger?
Mr. Fu.
Please don't do that.
I didn't do anything dangerous.
He can talk!
I can't believe you let a human in.
He really can talk!
Why in godforsaken hell?!
A Siberian tiger.
You think I'm some country bumpkin because of some words?!
There is no rule saying humans can't enter.
Mr. Fu, please don't make me intervene.
I loathe humans.
So cool!
This won't make me like humans!
But you wear human clothes.
Not with pleasure!
Then take them off.
Don't mess with me!
I swear I will devour her!
I must apologize for Mr. Fu's behavior.
Who is he?
Mr. Fu is a spirit, one of our clients.
What is this place, exactly?
Didn't Laojun tell about it?
No.
Then the hall manager will.
After all, it's his job.
What?
You say they have the Sky Pearl?
Indeed.
Are you sure?
When was the last time I was wrong?
Manager.
Lord Xuanli has arrived.
This hole is pretty deep.
What is he doing down there?
I'm Kali, the hall manager.
Welcome to our Spirit Club Hall,
Lord Xuanli.
Lord Xuanli is this person here.
Oh.
Stay with me - let's walk on, kicking pebbles as we go
Stay with me aruite yukou ishikoro wo kette
Our destination may be whimsical
Yukisaki wa kitto kimagure demo
But with the scent of flowers in both hands
Hana no kaori wo ryoute ni
I’ll carry it to the you I’ve yet to meet
kore kara deau kimi e to
Wait for me — let’s talk, side by side
Wait for me hanashi wo shiyou kata wo narabete
Even if our first “hello” is a little awkward
Hajimemashite wa gikochinaku temo
When we open the boxes we’ve brought
Mochiyotta hako aketara
Let’s share the dreams we’ve packed inside
Tsumekon da yume wo wakeaou
The days when we can casually say “See you tomorrow”
Mata ashita tte atarimae ni kawaseru hibi ga
Are so precious and so fleeting
Itoshikute hakanasugite
Those feelings will never fade away
Omoi wa kitto kienai
We can’t catch up to the clouds drifting across the sky
Sora wo nagareru kumo ni wa oitsukenai kedo
But they’ll turn to rain, bloom into flowers
Ame ni natte hana wo tsukete
And surely, they’re calling out to me
Kitto boku wo yonderu